Target Zoe
confirmed dead.
I asked Ching He's chairman for a favor.
This is a life-saving charm.
CHING HE TEMPLE
If you find yourself in danger,
use this to call Ching He.
There is evidence inside
that'll keep the Hsueh family in check.
Hello?
Gerald Chen told me
that if my life was in danger,
I should make this call.
If you're there,
save me and my daughter.
I understand.
I'll send someone right away.
THE FIXERS
FAKE, FORSAKEN, FRAUD
The fact Zoe's alive
isn't just bad for Yeh Yueh Tong.
It's also a threat
to the Hsueh clan.
-I won't hurt her.
-I know you won't do that.
At least not at the moment.
Meaning?
I can't predict
what you could do just to score points.
From the very beginning,
I was used by you to find her.
Isn't that right?
I've disobeyed my father
all my life. He can't stand me either.
You're right though.
If I was to bring Zoe home,
he'd think better of me.
You're right there.
-What are you gonna do?
-You first.
Fan sent a guy to kill Gerald.
She won't get away with it.
You're declaring war
on the whole of Yeh Yueh Tong?
Surely you've considered
how hard that's going to be?
How can I not do it?
Gerald is gone.
You don't have to follow him to the grave.
Don't lecture me.
-It's my life.
-You dying won't bring him back.
-You hear me?
-You ever had someone you care about?
BROTHER: DAD ISN'T WELL.
COME TO THE HOSPITAL QUICKLY.
What's going on with Dad?
The doctor says liver cancer.
It's metastasized.
Why didn't I hear about this earlier?
He told me not to tell you.
He didn't want you to worry.
He's not doing well today.
Don't rile him up, okay?
Dad. How are you doing?
All right.
I just had chemo.
I feel a bit off.
About my illness…
It must be kept quiet.
At a time like this, your health
is more important than politics.
Why didn't you tell me?
What about you?
When did you join Ching He?
Did you ever consider
that Thackery
let you join Ching He for a reason?
You working for him,
any time, anywhere,
he could use you as a pawn to threaten us.
You need to trust me.
If anything does happen,
I won't drag in the family.
Do you honestly think
I only worry about your brother?
You're also my son.
I often wonder…
did I show you enough care?
All my resources went into your brother.
That's why,
you did this as a challenge.
I was too hard on you,
when I think about it now.
I never gave you the opportunity to shine.
So all of this,
it was because you were afraid my real
identity might embarrass the family?
If I cared about all that,
why would I have kept you by my side?
I failed your mother.
Before she died,
I vowed to her
that I would do my best to raise you well.
I just hope that before you do anything,
don't rush into it.
Consider
the Hsueh clan.
I'm getting old.
The time I have left to watch you both,
it's running out.
Now,
you and Tristan,
look after each other.
Please.
Are you okay?
So you know
that I joined Ching He to become a fixer.
How'd you find out?
Dad didn't say who told him.
You know William's dead, right?
The news said he suicided.
He gassed himself in his car.
You didn't invest with him, did you?
The Hsin Nan redevelopment zone funds
were laundered through William.
Am I right?
How do you know that?
I have my sources.
The Hsin Nan redevelopment zone
is a huge cash cow.
Everyone in the party took a bribe.
Dad's political clout had eroded.
He needed to please the head honchos.
He had no choice.
He had to get his hands dirty.
Then why get Yeh Yueh Tong
to kill Zoe's family?
Zoe's husband, Hsu Ming-yi,
knew everything.
He tried to bribe Dad.
He even wanted Dad to back him
in his run for office.
Hsu Ming-yi also found out, uh,
about Dad's affair
with a student who then had you.
He blackmailed him.
Dad wanted to protect you.
As well as the Hsueh clan.
He had no other option.
That's when he went
to Yeh Yueh Tong for help.
He's not well now.
It's best just to let it go.
I'm gonna go see him before I go. You?
I'll stay a little.
AUTHENTIC TIEN-BU-LA
A new drug was discovered at the scene.
After ingesting it,
the user may experience
vomiting, diarrhea, or even fall into
an unconscious state, mimicking death.
Excuse me. Are you still serving?
Sorry, we're closed.
…investigating the origin
of this mysterious substance.
They are unsure of whether the drug itself
had actually been ingested by the victim…
Long time no see.
SHEN: BEN IS IN TROUBLE
GERALD CHEN, YEH YUEH TONG
MISSING, KIDNAPPED, DRUGS
At first,
in order to find Gerald,
you joined Yeh Yueh Tong.
I knew
as soon as I saw you
he had found an excellent trainee.
Let him go.
Where's Zoe?
If I just pull it out,
you do know what'll happen?
Why send someone to kill Gerald
and still get me to look for him?
We never found his body.
At first, I just wanted to know
if he was alive or dead.
Then I discovered Zoe,
to my horror, still wasn't dead.
Let him go!
And if you can, kill me.
You're just as good as Gerald,
yet somehow,
I have no trust in you.
Where is Zoe?
Don't tell her!
Even if you do tell her,
she… she won't let us go.
I'm sure you know
he can't hold on forever.
I have no idea.
I didn't expect that Zoe's life
would be more important than his.
I have no idea.
Please.
That's enough.
Let him go.
Louis Hsueh.
The Hsueh's second son.
-The pleasure is all mine.
-Let them go.
Let's just drop this.
Are all the Ching He fixers so cocky?
When Dad hears how very badly
Yeh Yueh Tong dealt with this,
how do you think he'll react?
Are you asking that
as a member of which clan?
Ching He or Hsueh?
What do you think?
You must know.
I'm the one
standing with the Hsueh family.
Mina,
his fate is due to your betrayal.
Gerald…
Did they really kill him?
This isn't your fault.
Y… You… You have to keep going.
Live your life.
When I see Gerald,
I…
I'll spell this out to him.
Mm-hmm.
The stall downstairs.
Okay.
I know.
Don't leave me!
Please don't leave me!
Shanghai Express.
Are you available to receive a package?
It's safe. You can speak.
Why'd you disappear?
The chairman's looking for you.
Ben's dead.
Say what?
Ben's dead?
We didn't find Gerald, but we found Zoe.
And I just rescued Mina from Madam Fan.
But I couldn't save Ben.
How did you find Zoe?
Gerald was sent by Yeh Yueh Tong
to kill Zoe.
He couldn't do it,
so they faked her death.
Now Madam Fan knows Zoe's alive,
she's going to finish the job.
No wonder the chairman
wants me to protect her.
-I'm on my way to pick her up.
-How did the chairman find out?
He didn't really explain.
I just have to bring her back.
Okay. Be careful.
Yeh Yueh Tong won't let go of this one.
Don't worry. If they wanna
take me out, they'll have to get in line.
Felix?
Mm-hmm. He's got Zoe.
He's taking her to Ching He.
How does Ching He know about Zoe?
Why are you asking me?
Get some rest. Then get on a plane tonight
and get out of here.
Who said I was leaving?
You think you'll be spared by Fan?
Ben was the only one I called family!
I'll get my revenge.
We don't know
why Ching He's looking for Zoe.
I don't want you
to get caught in the crossfire.
Are you worried about me?
Or the impact on the Hsueh clan?
Think what you like.
It's your life.
I just don't wanna collect your body
later, that's all.
I'll take care of this myself.
I won't bother you.
I thought you were an expert
at covering your tracks.
Louis knows we hired Yeh Yueh Tong.
Don't worry. I'll clean this up.
And I won't leave any loose ends.
Everything's in place regarding Thackery.
Let's not make any more errors.
What's wrong?
It's the sod-turning event.
Don't worry. Everything's been done.
I don't think, um,
I'm gonna make it
to the day you become mayor.
Dad, I got you the best doctor around.
If they can't find a cure,
we'll go abroad.
You can beat this.
I will make certain
that you see me climb to the top.
Not just mayor.
You… …I have never worried about.
Your brother, however,
that's another story.
As long as he's working for Ching He,
I will never rest.
Don't worry. He's a member
of the Hsueh clan.
Does he think of himself that way?
He became a fixer
without consulting me.
If you hadn't intervened,
I would have…
Dad.
Don't think about it.
Your health is the most important thing.
You know how Louis is.
You force him to quit now,
he'll only run further away.
I'd suggest you let him
stay with Ching He.
That could even benefit us in time.
Hm.
You… You haven't wasted all the mentoring
I gave you over the years.
I can only thank you for all your help.
Get some rest.
Leave everything to me.
Promise me.
Don't hurt your brother.
We're blood.
How could I do that?
It's been a long time
since you've come to offer incense.
I was last here
when my father was in control.
Coming back this time,
I had to prepare myself.
Hm.
This time, what would you
like to pray for?
All that I pray
is that I get what I'm owed.
Hm.
Everything I did
was for the benefit of Ching He.
Is that any different
to me and my father?
Lunar, we often find that,
if we upset the world's equilibrium,
well, then, good intentions can go wrong.
All I know
is that I won't back down again,
because I consider this my home.
Shall I see you out now?
I should be seeing you out.
Well, this is goodbye.
I'm sorry. Mr. Hsueh has to leave
for another appointment.
Embezzled funds have ended up
in the current mayor's hands. Comment?
I'm not in a position to speak on it.
It's under investigation.
But I do believe that, as a politician,
integrity, that's key.
-Will the party take disciplinary action?
-Please stop here. Thank you.
Do you think the mayor
should make an apology?
What kind of disciplinary
action might the party implement?
Mr. Huang, we're investigating
legislator Chao Ming-cheng's bribery case.
You're suspected of being a mediator.
Come to the station for questioning.
We have a search warrant. We're now
going to search Ching He Temple.
-All right, start the search.
-Yes sir.
There are new developments in
legislator Chao Ming-cheng's bribery case.
Investigators have begun
a second wave of searches.
This time, targeting
the chairman of Ching He, Thackery Huang.
Huang is suspected of being a middleman
in the bribery scheme.
He was taken in
for questioning earlier today.
-Sir, can you comment?
-I wanna talk to you in private.
Was it you who got Thackery arrested?
It was.
Are you helping Fan seize Ching He?
Ching He belonged to Madam Fan.
It's hardly seizing.
You're supporting Madam Fan?
It's more than just Dad's affairs.
Am I right?
I always said you were the smart one.
Dad never believed it.
What's your plan?
Ching He's Primordial Files.
I want them.
-You want those secret files?
-Correct.
The previous Fixer Celestial,
Madame Fan's dad,
he hid the Primordial Files.
They're in a secret room
in the Kuang Ming Chamber.
Only Madam Fan knows how to open it.
Not even Thackery knows.
So you want to get
the Primordial Files from Madam Fan.
She knows everything Dad's done.
If she reclaims Ching He,
she'll have absolute control.
We could never fight her off.
The files will give us
the necessary power.
We'd have influence
on both sides of the law.
Then neither Ching He nor Yeh Yueh Tong
could ever threaten the Hsueh clan.
Is this really necessary?
You don't have to help.
But if we don't succeed,
those you care about could be in danger.
First, we get rid of Thackery.
Then Madam Fan.
And Ching He, well,
I see you as its new leader.
I take charge of Ching He?
Only by standing at the top
and seizing the reins
can you possibly
save the ones you care about.
When I run this town,
and you control Ching He,
you'll be in the dark
while I'll be in the light.
Two brothers united.
I mean, who could possibly threaten us?
Howie,
does your dad really have Parkinson's?
Well, that's what he said.
He told me not to tell you.
Your dad speaks
a lot of nonsense sometimes--
He had a bag of pills.
Howie, listen to me.
I'll make sure he's looked after properly.
-You focus on your studies. Everything--
-What are you talking about?
I'll take care of him, too, all right?
Your dad's so stubborn.
The thing with the necklace
would have been fine,
but he had to put on an act
which made me think--
Hey.
Tell him you worked it out.
-Not that I squealed.
-I wouldn't do that.
Look at us. We're like two silly kids.
Oh. Ridiculous.
Oh. Felix forgot his keys.
How many times?
What's going on?
Car must have broken down.
The road's blocked. Wait in the car.
Hello there. I'm here for Felix.
What's this about?
We're business associates.
Associates in what?
How come I haven't heard anything
about a business before this?
-Is he not here?
-No, he's not.
How about you just leave me your phone
number and I'll have him contact you?
And your son? Where is he?
Uh, my son's out.
He's on a study date with his classmates.
You've lived in this house
for over 20 years, right?
We've lived here since we were married.
We've never moved.
That's so touching.
You and he…
All that love.
But you can't be sure.
I would suggest there are a lot of things
he doesn't share.
I told Felix,
inside this house, I run everything.
When it comes to his affairs outside,
I don't wanna know.
Nor will I get involved.
If you're done here,
I'd like you to leave--
I need to discuss
something important with Felix.
Dad, get back here. We're in danger.
HOWIE, TAKE CARE OF YOUR MOM.
TELL HER I'LL BE BACK SOON!
I'm gonna take a look. You stay here.
Okay.
Sorry. I've called roadside assistance.
My son has a fever.
I have to get him to the hospital.
I've been here two hours.
It shouldn't be too much longer.
I'll get you to a hospital.
Please listen.
You must look after her.
CHING HE TEMPLE
Take this.
Give it to Thackery Huang.
The images…
They…
have to do with….
CHING HE TEMPLE
…the Hsueh clan.
Oh.